Guide to the Stanford University, Registrar's Office, records SC1288
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, 1891-1999; Series 6 (Accession ARCH-2013-027)
  - 2. Aut. (Art - Hist.), 1956-1957; 95 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. (Hist. - M. Sc.), 1956-1957; 95 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. M. Sc. - Win. ASSL, 1956-1957; 95 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. (ASSL - Hist.), 1956-1957; 95 (Box 4)
  - 6. Win. (Hist. - Hist.), 1956-1957; 95 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Hist. - Spr. Educ., 1956-1957; 96 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (Educ. - G.RL), 1956-1957; 96 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (G.RL - Philos.), 1956-1957; 96 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. (Philos. - M. Sc.), 1956-1957; 96 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Pol. Sci. - Spr. M. Sci, 1956-1957; 97 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. (Air. Sci.), 1957-1958; 97 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. (Anthro), 1957-1958; 97 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. (Hist.), 1957-1958; 97 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. (Psych), 1957-1958; 97 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. (Stat - CE), 1957-1958; 98 (Box 4)
  - 2. Win. (EE - GRL), 1957-1958; 98 (Box 4)
  - 3. Win. (GRL - Poly Sci), 1957-1958; 98 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. (Psych. - Men's PE), 1957-1958; 98 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. (Women PE - M.E.), 1957-1958; 98 (Box 4)
  - 6. Spr. (Anthro. - Art), 1957-1958; 98 (Box 4)
  - 1. Spr. (ASSL - GRL), 1957-1958; 99 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (GRL - Philos), 1957-1958; 99 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (Phys. Sci. - Pete), 1957-1958; 99 (Box 4)
  - 4. Sum. (Air. Sci. - Speech), 1957-1958; 99 (Box 4)
  - 5. Sum. Geol. - Aut. Chem, 1957-1958; 99 (Box 4)
  - 1. Aut. (Chem. - Math), 1958-1959; 100 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. (Music - Geol.), 1958-1959; 100 (Box 4)
  - 3. Win. (G Ph. - Engr.), 1958-1959; 100 (Box 4)
  - 4. Win. (Anthro. - Hist.), 1958-1959; 100 (Box 4)
  - 5. Win. (Hist. - Geol.), 1958-1959; 100 (Box 4)
  - 1. Win. Geol. - Spr. A.E., 1958-1959; 101 (Box 4)
  - 2. Spr. (EE - Chem), 1958-1959; 101 (Box 4)
  - 3. Spr. (Classics - ME), 1958-1959; 101 (Box 4)
  - 4. Spr. (Hist. - Phys. Sci.), 1958-1959; 101 (Box 4)
  - 5. Spr. Physics - Sum. Women's PE, 1958-1959; 101 (Box 4)
  - 1. Sum. (Educ. - Met), 1958-1959; 102 (Box 4)
  - 2. Aut. (Air. Sci. - Asia), 1959-1960; 102 (Box 4)
  - 3. Aut. (Asia - Hist.), 1959-1960; 102 (Box 4)
  - 4. Aut. (Hum. - Law), 1959-1960; 102 (Box 4)
  - 5. Aut. (Anat. - Em), 1959-1960; 102 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports 1979/1980: 450.101-End, 113 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 4 1979: 020.374-378.241, Aug-83; 114 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1979: 380.070-630.393, Aug-83; 115 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1979 til Qtr. 1 1980: 3-79 832.300 - 1-80 390.802, Aug-83; 116 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 1/2 1980: 400.001-091.365, Aug-83; 117 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1980: 100.120-461.115, Aug-83; 118 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2/3 1980: 462.001-120.802, Aug-83; 119 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1980: 130.102-130.802, Aug-83; 120 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1980: 160.010-670.802, Aug-83; 121 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3/4 1980: 680.068-995.122, Aug-83; 122 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 1 1981: 007.001-999.091, Nov-84; 123 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1981: 007.001-390.802, Nov-84; 124 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1981: 400.001-999.200, Nov-84; 125 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1981: 007.001-400.192, Nov-84; 126 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1981: 020.103-997.199, Nov-84; 127 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1981: 400.196-999.093, Nov-84; 128 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 4 1981: 020.374-996.151, Nov-84; 129 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 1 1982: 007.001-390.325, Dec-85; 130 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 1 1982: 390.330-999.091, Dec-85; 131 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1982: 007.001-400.198, Dec-85; 132 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1982: 400.198-999.092, Dec-85; 133 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1982: 007.001-530.182, Dec-85; 134 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1982: 530.200-999.093, Dec-85; 135 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1982: 007.001-997.165 (Grad), Dec-85; 136 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 4 1982: 020.374-991.016, Dec-87; 137 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 1 1983: 007.001-360.802, Dec-87; 138 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 1 1983: 371.101-700.801, Dec-87; 139 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1983: 007.001-400.802, Dec-87; 140 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 2 1983: 401.001-994.058, Dec-87; 141 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1983: 050.201-780.801, Dec-87; 142 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1983: 400.030-999.093, Dec-87; 143 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 3 1983: 020.136-997.199, Dec-87; 144 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Qtr. 4 1983: 020.374-996.183, Dec-87; 145 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 84/85: 007-378, 31_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 84/85:780-999, May-90; 33_80 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Winter 84/85: 020-360, Nov-88; 34_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Winter 84/85: 020-360, May-90; 34_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Winter 84/85: 360-740, May-90; 35_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Winter 84/85: 360-740, Nov-88; 35_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Winter 84/85: 740-920, May-90; 36_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Winter 84/85: 740-920, Nov-88; 36_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Spring 84/85: 007-400, Nov-88; 37_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Spring 84/85: 007-400, May-90; 37_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Spring 84/85: 400-999, Nov-88; 38_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Spring 84/85: 400-999, May-90; 38_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Spring 84/85: 020-997, Nov-88; 39_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Spring 84/85: 020-997, May-90; 39_88 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Summer 84/85: 020-980, May-90; 40_88 (Box 4)
  - EQR - Grade Cards 59/60: Autumn - Winter, Jan-90; 1 (Box 4)
  - EQR - Grade Cards 59/60: Spring - Summer, Jan-90; 2 (Box 4)
  - EQR - Grade Cards 60/61: Autumn, Jan-90; 3 (Box 4)
  - EQR - Grade Cards 60/61: Winter - Spring, Jan-90; 4 (Box 4)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 84/85: 007-378, Nov-88; 31_88 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 84/85: 380-780, Nov-88; 32_88 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 84/85: 380-780, May-90; 32_88 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 84/85: 780-999, Nov-88; 33_88 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 84/85: 020-980, Nov-88; 40_88 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 85/86: 007-350, Oct-91; 1 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 85/86: 350-999, Oct-91; 2 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 85/86: 020-390, Oct-91; 3 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 85/86: 400-999, Oct-91; 4 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 85/86: 007-390, Oct-91; 5 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 85/86: 400-997, Oct-91; 6 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 85/86: 007-997, Oct-91; 7 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 85/86: 020-991, Oct-91; 8 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 86/87: 007-360, Oct-91; 9 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 86/87: 371-999, Oct-91; 10 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 86/87: 020-351, Oct-91; 11 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 86/87: 360-999, Oct-91; 12 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 86/87: 007-380, Oct-91; 13 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 86/87: 390-999, Oct-91; 14 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 86/87: 020-997, Oct-91; 15 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 86/87: 020-991, Oct-91; 16 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 87/88: 007-372, Oct-91; 17 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 87/88: 373-999, Oct-91; 18 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 87/88: 020-360, Oct-91; 19 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 87/88: 371-999, Oct-91; 20 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 87/88: 020-400, Oct-91; 21 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 87/88: 401-999, Oct-91; 22 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 87/88: 020-997, Oct-91; 23 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 87/88: 020-988, Oct-91; 24 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 88/89: 020-340, Oct-91; 25 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 88/89: 350-997, Oct-91; 26 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Witner 88/89: 020-390, Oct-91; 27 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 88/89: 400-999, Oct-91; 28 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 88/89: 020-420, Oct-91; 29 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 88/89: 430-999, Oct-91; 30 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 88/89: 020-997, Oct-91; 31 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 88/89: 020-997, Oct-91; 32 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 89/90: 020-371, Oct-91; 33 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 89/90: 372-999, Oct-91; 34 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 89/90: 020-407, Oct-91; 35 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 89/90: 410-999, Oct-91; 36 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 89/90: 020-420, Oct-91; 37 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 89/90: 430-999, Oct-91; 38 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 89/90: 020-997, Oct-91; 39 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 89/90: 020-997, Oct-91; 40 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 90/91, Apr-92; 41 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 90/91, Apr-92; 42 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 90/91, Apr-92; 43 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 90/91, Apr-92; 44 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 90/91, Apr-92; 45 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 90/91, Apr-92; 46 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports 90/91: 020-511, Aug-92; 47 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 90/91, Apr-92; 48 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports: 020-300, Aug-92; "48" (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports: 400-999, Aug-92; "49" (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 91/92: 020-300, Aug-92; "50" (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 91/92: 400-999, Aug-92; "51" (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 91/92: 020-482, 53 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 91/92: 511-999, 54 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 91/92: 020-999, 55 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 91/92: 020-980, 56 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 92/93: 020-390, 1 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 92/93: 400-999, 2 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 92/93: 020-351, 3 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 92/93: 330-999, 4 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 92/93: 020-999, 5 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 92/93: 020-997, 6 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 1993, 7 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 1993, 8 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 1993, 9 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 92/93: 020-980, 10 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Autumn 94/95: 020-482, 1 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Autumn 94/95: 020-482, 2 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Autumn 94/95: 511-999, 3 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Winter 94/95: 020-482, 4 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Winter 94/95: 511-99, 6 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Spring 94/95: 020-596, 8 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Spring 94/95: 620-999, 9 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Spring 94/95: 020-995, 10 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Summer 94/95: 020-995, 11 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 95/96: 020-280, 1 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 95/96: 300-482, 2 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 95/96: 511-725, 3 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Autumn 95/96: 700, 4 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 95/96: 020-320, 5 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 95/96: 325-482, 6 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Winter 95/96: 511-999, 7 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 95/96: 020-247, 8 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 95/96: 247-580, 9 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 95/96: 580-999, 10 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 95/96: 020-988, 11 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Spring 95/96: 700, 12 (Box 5)
  - Grade Reports Summer 95/96: 026-995, 13 (Box 5)
  - Student Records Autumn 98/99: 020-390, 1 (Box 5)
  - End Quarter Reports: 1987-88/1992-93, 4 (Box 5)
  - Spring, Summer, 4 (Box 5)
- Records, 1951-1982; Series 7 (Accession 2001-123)
  Notebook kept between 1951 and 1982 with information on the establishment of programs and departments, subsequent changes, and the dates of the first graduate degrees conferred.
  - Notebook, 1951-1982 (Box 1)
- Records, 1905-1926; Series 8 (Accession ARCH-1990-035)
  - Letter from Mary C. Sweet, assistant registrar, to G.L. Aynesworth, concerning his daughters' applications to Stanford, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Receipt to John E. Carpenter for laboratory fees, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Registration certificate and transcript for Chester Lloyd Proebstel, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Records, 1891-2004; Series 9 (Accession ARCH-2016-113)
  - Microfilm Records
    - Credential Files: 1-83 (Aaron-Kohn), 1891-1964 (Box 1)
    - Credential Files: 84-161 (Kohner-Wieden), 1891-1964 (Box 2)
    - Credential Files: 162-245 (Wiedley-Fudge), 1891-1964 (Box 3)
    - Credential Files: 246-329 (Fudge-Mixter), 1891-1964 (Box 4)
    - Credential Files: 330-419 (Miyashita-White), 1891-1964 (Box 5)
    - Credential Files: 420-509 (White-Duffy), 1891-1964 (Box 6)
    - Credential Files: 510-599 (Duggan-Bishop), 1891-1964 (Box 7)
    - Credential Files: 600-689 (Bishop-Smith), 1891-1964 (Box 8)
    - Credential Files: 690-779 (Smith-Farrar), 1891-1964 (Box 9)
    - Credential Files: 780-868 (Farrell-Clark), 1891-1964 (Box 10)
    - Credential Files: 869-958 (Fenselau-Barricks), 1891-1964 (Box 11)
    - Credential Files: 959-996 (Barrows-Zulevic), 1891-1964 (Box 12)
    - Inactive Doctoral Degree Candidates: 1-2, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
    - Inactive Master's Degree Candidates, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
    - Doctoral Degrees Conferred: 1-4, 1988-1996 (Box 12)
    - War Training Files: 1-7 (Abernathy-Zweig), 1942-1944 (Box 12)
    - Summer Session Applications: 1-3, 1982-1993 (Box 12)
    - Final Recommending and Distinction Lists: 1-7, 1947-2004 (Box 12)
    - Medical Post Documents: 1-2, 1983-1991 (Box 12)
    - Graduate Degrees Conferred: 1-10, 1983-1991 (Box 12)
    - Master's Degrees Conferred, 1988-1995 (Box 12)
    - AB/BA/BAS Degrees Advanced Degrees, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - Master's Engineer DMA Degrees, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
    - Nursing: (A-Z), 1989 (Box 12)
    - Credential Files: 1-11 (Aandahl-Marshall), 1927-1948 (Box 12)
    - Credential Files: 12-49 (Marshall-Wittson), undated (Box 13)
    - Student Record Cards: 1-48 (Amaral-Zyre), 1891-1958 (Box 13)
    - Transcripts: 1-3 (Aaron-Burnhill), 1930-1954 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Transcripts Degrees Conferred, 1891-1996 (Box 14)
  - Volumes
    - Stanford Register, Part 1: Staff Student Summaries, 1947-1948 (Box 17)
    - Stanford Register, Part 2: Courses, 1947-1948 (Box 17)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1: Staff Student Summaries, 1949-1950 (Box 18)
    - Stanford Register, Part 2: Courses, 1949-1950 (Box 18)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1: Students Summaries; Degrees Granted, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
    - Stanford Register, Part 2: Course Enrollment; Instructor Assignment, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1: Student's Summaries; Degrees Granted, 1964-1965 (Box 17)
    - Stanford Register, Part 2: Course Enrollment; Instructor Assignment, 1964-1965 (Box 15)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1, Section 1: Summaries; Degrees Granted; Students, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1, Section 2: Summaries; Degrees Granted; Students, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - Stanford Register, Part 2: Course Enrollment; Instructor Assignment, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1, Section 1: Summaries; Degrees Granted; Students, 1966-1967 (Box 16)
    - Stanford Register: Course Enrollment, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
    - Stanford Register, Part 1, Section 1: Summaries; Degrees Granted; Students, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Box 20)
- Records, 1984-1985; Series 10 (Accession ARCH-2017-067)
  - Transcripts, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Records, 1880-1918; Series 11
  Letters (mostly incoming) to the Office of the Registrar, David Starr Jordan, and Orrin Leslie Elliott. Most are requests for course catalogs or information about academic programs, also includes general correspondence, and requests for academic records.
  - Correspondence, 1880-1892 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1893-1896 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1898-1899 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1900-1902 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, 1903-1904 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, 1905-1906 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1906-1907 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, 1907-1908 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, 1908-1909 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, 1912-1913 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, 1913 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, 1914-1918 (Box 16)
  - Letters - Vaccination Records, 1908-1914 (Box 16)
- Records, 1920s-1971; Series 12 (Accession ARCH-1997-180)
  Undergraduate admission ledgers maintained by the Office of the Registrar. Includes name of high school, initial year performance report with GPA and unit totals.
  Ledgers are restricted for 75 years from date of creation.
  - Admissions Ledger - Freshmen, Alabama - California, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Ledger - Freshmen, Colorado - Montana, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Ledger - Freshmen, Nebraska - Wyoming, Foreign, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Ledger - Freshmen, Alabama - California (1 of 2), 1968-1971 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Ledger - Freshmen, Alabama - California (2 of 2), 1968-1971 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Ledger - Transfers (3 year record), 1967-1970 (Box 2)
  - Admissions Ledger - Freshman Applicants (L-Z), 1971 (Box 2)
  - Admissions Ledger - California L-R, 1954-1966 (Box 2)
  - Admissions Ledger - California S-Z, 1954-1966 (Box 2)
  - Admissions Ledger - Private High Schools C.E.E. Board, 1920s-1960s (Box 3)
  - Admissions Ledger - Public High Schools, 1920s-1960s (Box 4)
  - Admissions Ledger - Public High Schools, 1920s-1960s (Box 5)
  - Admissions Ledger - Public High Schools, 1920s-1960s (Box 6)